{
    "categories": [],
    "description": "Name the cartoons that featured these famous villains.",
    "difficulty": -1,
    "questions": [{
        "answer": "Peter Pan",
        "category": "Cartoon Villains Quiz",
        "question": "Captain Hook"
    }, {
        "answer": "Batman",
        "category": "Cartoon Villains Quiz",
        "question": "The Joker"
    }, {
        "answer": "The Lion King",
        "category": "Cartoon Villains Quiz",
        "question": "Scar"
    }, {
        "answer": "101 Dalmatians",
        "category": "Cartoon Villains Quiz",
        "question": "Cruella de Vil"
    }, {
        "answer": "Aladdin",
        "category": "Cartoon Villains Quiz",
        "question": "Jafar"
    }, {
        "answer": "The Little Mermaid",
        "category": "Cartoon Villains Quiz",
        "question": "Ursula"
    }, {
        "answer": "SpongeBob SquarePants",
        "category": "Cartoon Villains Quiz",
        "question": "Plankton"
    }, {
        "answer": "Road Runner",
        "category": "Cartoon Villains Quiz",
        "question": "Wile E. Coyote"
    }, {
        "answer": "Transformers",
        "category": "Cartoon Villains Quiz",
        "question": "Megatron"
    }, {
        "answer": "X-Men",
        "category": "Cartoon Villains Quiz",
        "question": "Magneto"
    }, {
        "answer": "Sleeping Beauty",
        "category": "Cartoon Villains Quiz",
        "question": "Maleficent"
    }, {
        "answer": "Spider-Man",
        "category": "Cartoon Villains Quiz",
        "question": "Dr. Octopus"
    }, {
        "answer": "Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles",
        "category": "Cartoon Villains Quiz",
        "question": "Shredder"
    }, {
        "answer": "The Simpsons",
        "category": "Cartoon Villains Quiz",
        "question": "Sideshow Bob"
    }, {
        "answer": "The Smurfs",
        "category": "Cartoon Villains Quiz",
        "question": "Gargamel"
    }, {
        "answer": "G.I. Joe",
        "category": "Cartoon Villains Quiz",
        "question": "Cobra Commander"
    }, {
        "answer": "Masters of the Universe",
        "category": "Cartoon Villains Quiz",
        "question": "Skeletor"
    }, {
        "answer": "The Powerpuff Girls",
        "category": "Cartoon Villains Quiz",
        "question": "Mojo Jojo"
    }, {
        "answer": "Popeye",
        "category": "Cartoon Villains Quiz",
        "question": "Bluto"
    }, {
        "answer": "Captain Planet",
        "category": "Cartoon Villains Quiz",
        "question": "Captain Pollution"
    }, {
        "answer": "Inspector Gadget",
        "category": "Cartoon Villains Quiz",
        "question": "Dr. Claw"
    }, {
        "answer": "Rocky & Bullwinkle",
        "category": "Cartoon Villains Quiz",
        "question": "Boris & Natasha"
    }, {
        "answer": "ThunderCats",
        "category": "Cartoon Villains Quiz",
        "question": "Mumm-Ra"
    }, {
        "answer": "Darkwing Duck",
        "category": "Cartoon Villains Quiz",
        "question": "Negaduck"
    }],
    "quizLength": 24,
    "title": "Cartoon Villains Quiz",
    "url": "http://www.jetpunk.com/quizzes/cartoon-villains-quiz.php"
}